Guide to the School of Forestry and Environmental Studies, Yale University, Records of the Dean
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Records, 1985-2010; Accession 2014-A-075
  - Records of Dean Gus Speth
    - Transparencies - FES, Undated (Box 7, Folder 39)
    - Transportation and the Environment, 2001 January (Box 7, Folder 40)
    - Trends - 2003, 2002 October - 2003 August (Box 7, Folder 41)
    - Trends - Sept 2005, 2005 September (Box 7, Folder 42)
    - Trends - 2007, 2007 September (Box 7, Folder 43)
    - Trend Data 2008, 2008 August (Box 7, Folder 44)
    - Tropical Resources - Annual Report 2001, 1998 June - 2001 July (Box 7, Folder 45)
    - Tropical Resources Institute (TRI), 1993 January - 1997 July (Box 7, Folder 46)
    - TRI Committee, 1998 June (Box 7, Folder 47)
    - Undergraduate Committees, 2002 February (Box 7, Folder 48)
    - Undergraduate Courses, 2000 December - 2001 May (Box 7, Folder 49)
    - University Council Meeting for FES (5/5/1995), 1995 March-April (Box 7, Folder 50)
    - University Council Final Report, 1989 November - 1995 October (Box 7, Folder 51)
    - Urban Gradient, 2007 January (Box 7, Folder 52)
    - Urban Resources Initiative (1), 1995 April - 2002 September (Box 7, Folder 53)
    - Urban Resources Initiative (2), 1989 December - 1995 February (Box 7, Folder 54)
    - US-Asia Environmental Partnership, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 55)
    - Vehicles, 1992 July - 1999 May (Box 7, Folder 57)
    - Vermont Law/FES, 2000 March - 2001 December (Box 7, Folder 58)
    - Video of School, 2000 November - 2001 December (Box 7, Folder 59)
    - Visiting Faculty, 2002 April (Box 7, Folder 60)
    - Visiting Lecturers - Yearly, 2001 December - 2002 June (Box 7, Folder 61)
    - Video, 2000 November - 2001 January (Box 7, Folder 62)
    - Visiting Faculty, 2000 April (Box 7, Folder 63)
    - Visiting Fellows, 1993 May - 2002 February (Box 7, Folder 64)
    - Water Museum, 2002 October - 2003 August (Box 7, Folder 65)
    - West Indian/FES Initiative in Trinidad, 2003 March (Box 7, Folder 66)
    - Weyerhaeuser Program, 1991 July - 2001 May (Box 7, Folder 67)
    - Weyerhaeuser Center for Forest Management, 1993 January - 1993 June (Box 7, Folder 68)
    - Women and Environment Organization, 1994 August (Box 7, Folder 69)
    - Women in Leadership Project, 1998 September - 1998 October (Box 7, Folder 70)
    - Working Group Communications, 2000 January (Box 7, Folder 71)
    - Working Group/Centennial Campaign, 1999 November - 2000 February (Box 7, Folder 72)
    - Workloads/Professors at FES, 2002 January - 2002 February (Box 7, Folder 73)
    - World Fellows Seminar, 2005 July (Box 7, Folder 74)
    - World Summit on Sustainable Development, 2001 March (Box 7, Folder 75)
    - Working Group - Yale College, 1999 November - 2000 March (Box 7, Folder 76)
    - Yale College-FES Joint Bachelor's-Master's Program, 2000 July (Box 7, Folder 77)
    - Yale College - Joint Degree, 2001 December - 2002 January (Box 7, Folder 78)
    - Yale Environment OnLine, 2006 May - 2006 July (Box 7, Folder 79)
    - American Forest and Paper Association; 1995 Dean's Tour, 1996 - 2002 (Box 7, Folder 80)
    - Blue Planet Nomination - 2004, 2004 October (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Blue Planet Prize - 2006, 2007 February (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Blue Planet Prize - 2007, 2006 July-August (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - (Brown) Lyons Brown Foundation, 2005 July (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Center for Humans and Nature, 2007 June (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Compton Foundation, 2000 October - 2003 April (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Connecticut Agricultural Experiment Station, March 1994 - May 2004 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Cross Current Productions, 2001 January (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Doris Duke Foundation, 1999 November - 2003 September (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Elms Fellowship (see also "Idaho Fish and Game"), 1993 December - 1995 August (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - English Station Power Plant, 2000 June (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Yale Environment Poll, 2004 May (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Evan Frankel Foundation, 2000 December - 2003 July (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Forest Conservation, 2005 December (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Forest Endowment Board of Advisors Meeting - Oct 2002, 2002 October (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Forest History Society, 2002 July - 2002 September (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - Forestland Group, 1996 July - 2000 December (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - Forest Service IPA, 2001 January (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - Forests, John Berger, 2005 August (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - Fuel Cells, 2001 August - 2001 September (Box 8, Folder 33)
    - Gaia Atlas, 2004 April (Box 8, Folder 34)
    - Gates Foundation\Melissa Chan, 2000 April - 2003 October (Box 8, Folder 35)
    - Gaylord Donnelley Environmental Fellowship Program, 1999 April - 2004 February (Box 8, Folder 36)
    - General Electric, 2002 April - 2003 June (Box 8, Folder 38)
    - Glaser Family Foundation, The, 2000 August-September (Box 8, Folder 40)
    - Global Consortium for Higher Education, 2007 March (Box 8, Folder 41)
    - Global Environment Facility (GEF), 2002 September - 2003 September (Box 8, Folder 42)
    - Global Heritage, 2003 February-April (Box 8, Folder 43)
    - Global Nomads Group, Inc. (includes DVD), 2000 November - 2001 August (Box 8, Folder 44)
    - Goldman Fund, 2000 February - 2003 March (Box 8, Folder 46)
    - HBO -- Too Hot to Handle (6/26), 2006 May-June (Box 8, Folder 47)
    - Hale and Dorr, 2002 April - 2003 June (Box 8, Folder 49)
    - Hannover Principles: Design for Sustainability, 37530 (Box 8, Folder 51)
    - Hanrahan, Brendan--EarthNet, 2006 August-December (Box 8, Folder 52)
    - HARC (Houston Advanced Research Center), 2002 February-March (Box 8, Folder 53)
    - Harder and Company, 2001 January-March (Box 8, Folder 54)
    - Harvard University, 1998 March - 2001 February (Box 8, Folder 60)
    - Harvard University\Center for Environment, 2002 March-April (Box 8, Folder 61)
    - Hastings Center, 1999 September - 2002 August (Box 8, Folder 63)
    - Heinz Foundation, 2000 January - 2002 October (Box 8, Folder 68)
    - Heinz, Theresa/Scholars for Environmental Research, 1998 April - 2001 February (Box 8, Folder 69-70)
    - Heldref Publications, 36982 (Box 8, Folder 71)
    - Herald (Yale Herald; Newspaper), 37104 (Box 8, Folder 73)
    - Hewlett, 2000 May - 2003 March (Box 8, Folder 76)
    - Hewlett Foundation, 2002 December - 2003 April (Box 8, Folder 77)
    - Hewlett-Packard, 2000 May - 2003 March (Box 8, Folder 78)
    - Hoffer Proposal, 2000 January-August (Box 8, Folder 82)
    - Home Depot, 2000 September - 2003 August (Box 8, Folder 85)
    - Horizon's, 1999 October - 2001 October (Box 8, Folder 87)
    - HR 882, 2001 December - 2002 September (Box 8, Folder 91)
    - Hubbard Brook Research Foundation, 1997 - 2003 (Box 8, Folder 92)
    - Hudson River, 2001 July - 2002 September (Box 8, Folder 94)
    - Hudson Task Force, 2000 June - 2002 February (Box 8, Folder 95)
    - Hue-New Haven Sister Cities, 2000 September (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Human Impact Foundation, 2002 February (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Human Population and Freshwater Workshop, 2000 October - 2001 March (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - International Development Conference, 1999 December (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - IGES (Institute for Global Environmental Strategies) Board, 2002 March - 2004 June (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - IGES (Institute for Global Environmental Strategies) 1 of 4, 2000 August - 2003 January (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - IGES (Institute for Global Environmental Strategies) 2 of 4, 2003 February (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - IGES (Institute for Global Environmental Strategies) 3 of 4, 2003 February - 2004 April (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - IGES (Institute for Global Environmental Strategies) 4 of 4, 2004 May - 2005 February (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - India Council for Sustainable Development, 2006 November - 2007 April (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Institute for International Economics, 2001 October (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Institute for River Research/Long Island Sound, 2000 May (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - IPCC (Intergovernmental Panel on Climate Change) "Climate Change 2007", 2007 February (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Intergovernmental Panel on Global Environmental Change, 2002 October - 2003 February (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - International Centre for Rainforest Conservation and Development, 2000 August - 2003 January (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - International Center for Sustainable Development (CIDES), 2003 November (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - International Food Policy Research (IFPRI), 2001 March (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - International Festival of Arts and Ideas, 2000 January - 2002 May (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - International Fund for Agricultural Development, 2001 July (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - Inter-American Development Bank, 1999 December - 2000 January (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - International Development Conference, 1999 July - 2000 June (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - International Institute for Sustainable Development (IISD), 2006 June (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - International Plant Genetic Resources Institute, 2002 September (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - International Sustainable Development Foundation, 2002 May (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - International Union of Forestry Research Organizations (IUFRO), 1998 July - 2008 February (Box 9, Folder 29)
    - Initiative on Science and Technology for Sustainability, 2002 June - 2002 July (Box 9, Folder 30)
    - IPCC Report/Speth, Gus, 2001 October (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - Island Press, 2001 March (Box 9, Folder 32)
    - Island Press--Contract/Globalization and the Environment, 2002 January - 2002 February (Box 9, Folder 33)
    - Italian Embassy, Washington, D.C., 2002 January - 2002 March (Box 9, Folder 34)
    - Ittleson Foundation, 2001 July (Box 9, Folder 35)
    - IUCN Academy of Environmental Law, 2000 May (Box 9, Folder 36)
    - IUCN - Pace University, 2007 January-June (Box 9, Folder 37)
    - IUCN, 2006 October (Box 9, Folder 38)
    - IUCN Advisory Group, 2004 April-November (Box 9, Folder 39)
    - IUCN WSSD Advisory Group, 2001 November-December (Box 9, Folder 40)
    - Japan, 2000 February - 2000 April (Box 9, Folder 43)
    - Japan\World Bank Scholarship Program, 2001 December (Box 9, Folder 44)
    - Jeffrey Trust, 2001 January (Box 9, Folder 46)
    - Johnson Foundation, The, 2002 June (Box 9, Folder 51)
    - Johnson, Nancy (Congresswoman), 36861 (Box 9, Folder 52)
    - "K" Correspondence, 1992 August - 2003 March (Box 9, Folder 57)
    - Kerry, John, 2002 August (Box 9, Folder 67)
    - Keystone Center - Correspondence, 1999 August - 2002 June (Box 9, Folder 68)
    - Keystone Center - File 1 of 4, 1999 October - 2000 June (Box 9, Folder 69)
    - Keystone Center - File 2 of 4, 2001 June - 2001 December (Box 9, Folder 70)
    - Keystone Center - File 3 of 4, 2001 January (Box 9, Folder 71)
    - Keystone Center - File 4 of 4, 2002 January - 2002 June (Box 9, Folder 72)
    - Landscape\Knobloch Project, 2007 October (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Korean Pine Forests, 2000 October (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Lamar Center, 2000 August (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Leadership for Environment and Development (LEAD), 2000 February - 2000 November (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - League of Conservation Voters, 1999 October - 2003 December (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Luce Foundation, 2000 July - 2006 August (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Alpha "M" (Dean's Correspondence), 2002-2003 (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - MacArthur Foundation, 1997 April - 2005 July (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - Martin Institute, 2005 June (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - Mellon Foundation, October 1997 - February 2001 (Box 10, Folder 40)
    - Men's Resource Center, 2001 November-December (Box 10, Folder 41)
    - Merck Family Fund, 2000 January - 2002 May (Box 10, Folder 42)
    - Meridian Institute, 2000 August (Box 10, Folder 43)
    - Mexico City Commission, 37530 (Box 10, Folder 44)
    - Milken Global Conference, 36923 (Box 10, Folder 47)
    - Mill River Watershed Association, 36557 (Box 10, Folder 48)
    - Millenium Ecosystem Assessment Advisory Group, 2001 January - 2002 December (Box 10, Folder 49)
    - Mississippi State University Forest and Wildlife Research Center, 38078 (Box 10, Folder 53)
    - Missouri Botanical Garden, 1999 December - 2003 April (Box 10, Folder 54)
    - MIT Press, 2002 December - 2003 March (Box 10, Folder 55)
    - Monte Mediterraneo Foundation, 2002 November - 2003 January (Box 10, Folder 57)
    - Moore Visit - March 7, 2002, 2001 November - 2002 March (Box 10, Folder 60)
    - Moore Foundation, 2002 April - 2007 April (Box 10, Folder 61)
    - Moore Foundation Proposal - File 1 of 2, 2002 April-June (Box 10, Folder 62)
    - Moore Foundation Proposal - File 2 of 2, 2002 May-November (Box 10, Folder 63)
    - Multilateral Development Banks (MDBs), 36892 (Box 10, Folder 64)
    - Murray Pacific Corporation, 1994 January - 2001 December (Box 10, Folder 66)
    - Museum of Life and Environment, 38353 (Box 10, Folder 67)
    - Alpha "N" (Dean's Correspondence), 1993 March - 2002 November (Box 10, Folder 69)
    - National Association of Professional Forestry Schools and Colleges, 1999 September - 2002 March (Box 10, Folder 71)
    - NAS Committee (National Acadamies Transition to Sustainability/Coordinating Committee), 2000 December (Box 10, Folder 72)
    - NASA Funding, 1999 March (Box 10, Folder 73)
    - Nation, The (Subscription), 2002 November (Box 10, Folder 75)
    - National Academics, 2000 August - 2002 September (Box 10, Folder 76)
    - National Academies, 2001 February (Box 10, Folder 77)
    - National Academy of Engineering, 2000 September - 2000 October (Box 10, Folder 78)
    - National Academy of Public Administration, 2000 May (Box 10, Folder 79)
    - National Academy of Sciences, 1993 January - 2000 November (Box 10, Folder 80)
    - National Academies, The: Science, Technology and Law Program, 2003 September (Box 10, Folder 81)
    - National Assessment Overview, 2000 December (Box 10, Folder 82)
    - National Association of State Foresters (Addresses, Etc.), Undated (Box 10, Folder 83)
    - National Audubon Society, 1987 April- 2001 August (Box 10, Folder 84)
    - National Committee on U.S.-China Relations, 2004 November (Box 10, Folder 85)
    - National Council for Science and the Environment, 2001 October - 2003 October (Box 10, Folder 86)
    - National Religious Partnership for the Environment, 2002 August (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - National Research Council, Undated (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Natural Resources Council of America, 1999 September - 2002 November (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - National University of Singapore (NUS Trip), 2004 January (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - NRDC Mission Statement, 2000 August - 2007 January (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Nature Magazine (Subscriptions), 1998 October - 2003 January (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Nature Conservancy - Maine Chapter, 1997 September - 2001 March (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Nature Conservancy #1, 1992 October - 2003 May (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Nature Publishing Group, 2001 January (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - NEPA News (see also National Resources Council of America), 2001 February-October (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - New England Campus Environmental Leadership Summit, 2003 February (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - New England Forestry Foundation, 2002 January-November (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - New Haven, City of, 2001 October - 2004 February (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - New Haven Air Toxics Project, 2002 October (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - New Haven Committee, 1992 August (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - New Haven Environment, 2000 October (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - New Haven Foundation, 2001 April (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - New Haven Harbor, 2001 October (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - New Haven Watersheds, 2000 October (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - New Scientist, 2003 January (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - New York Botanical Garden, 2000 March (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - New York Times, 2003 January (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - (Edward John) Noble Foundation, Inc., 2002 June (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - Northern Arizona University, 2000 January - 2001 January (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - Northern Power Presentation, 2002 September (Box 11, Folder 29)
    - Alpha "O" (Dean's Correspondence), 1993 - 1996 (Box 11, Folder 30)
    - Oceana, Undated (Box 11, Folder 31)
    - Office of New Haven Affairs, 2000 October (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - Oklahoma State University, 2001 February (Box 11, Folder 36)
      Folder not received
    - Open Space Institute, 1996 May - 2003 October (Box 11, Folder 37)
    - Organisation for Economic Co-Operation and Development, 1999 October - 2004 September (Box 11, Folder 40)
    - Organization for Tropical Studies, 2002 October (Box 11, Folder 41)
    - Outward Bound, 2001 June (Box 11, Folder 47)
    - Oxford Forestry Institute, 2002 January (Box 11, Folder 48)
    - Alpha "P" - Dean's Correspondence, 2003 October (Box 11, Folder 49)
    - Pace University, 2001 December - 2004 April (Box 11, Folder 50)
    - Pacific Forest Trust, 1998 May - 2002 September (Box 11, Folder 52)
    - Packard Fellowship, 1996 February - 1996 April (Box 11, Folder 53)
    - Packard Foundation, 2000 May - 2004 October (Box 11, Folder 54)
    - Partners for Livable Communities, 2001 September - 2002 January (Box 11, Folder 59)
    - Pastrana Borrero Lecture, 2000 October (Box 11, Folder 60)
    - Pataki, George (see Hudson Task Force), 2000 April-May (Box 11, Folder 61)
    - Patrick Center, 2000 May - 2006 June (Box 11, Folder 62)
    - Paulson, Hank, 2002 July (Box 11, Folder 63)
    - Penn State Indicators Report 2000, Undated (Box 11, Folder 65)
    - Pew Center, 2000 August - 2002 April (Box 11, Folder 68)
    - Pew Initiative on Food and Biotechnology, 2001 August (Box 11, Folder 69)
    - Pinchot Institute - Correspondence, 1999 December - 2003 March (Box 11, Folder 72)
    - Pinchot Institute - Board of Directors - June 2000, 2000 June - 2001 September (Box 11, Folder 73)
    - Pinchot Institute - Board of Directors - Feb 2001, 2001 February (Box 11, Folder 74)
    - Pinchot Institute - Board of Directors - Apr 2001, 2001 April (Box 11, Folder 75)
    - Pinchot Institute - Board of Directors - Aug 2001, 2000 August (Box 11, Folder 76)
    - Pinchot Institute Grey Towers/General Correspondence, Etc., 2000 June - 2001 September (Box 11, Folder 77)
    - Pinchot Institute Grey Towers/Visiting Fellows Program, 2000 February (Box 11, Folder 78)
    - Pinchot - Scholarship Awards Committee, 2000 January-December (Box 11, Folder 79)
    - Pinchot Institute for Conservation Studies, 2001 January-October (Box 11, Folder 80)
    - Pinchot Institute - Forestry Education, 1999 June (Box 11, Folder 81)
    - Pinchot Institute - Board of Directors - Feb 2000, 2000 February (Box 11, Folder 82)
    - Pinchot Memorial, 1999 November (Box 11, Folder 83)
    - Pitney Bowes, 2003 March (Box 11, Folder 84)
    - Plum Creek Timber, 2003 February-April (Box 11, Folder 85)
    - Policy Sciences Center, 2000 August-December (Box 11, Folder 86)
    - Population Action International, 2005 October - 2008 January (Box 11, Folder 87)
    - Poynter Fellows, 2001 April (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Presidential Management Intern, 2001 September (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Prince of Wales Management Committee, 2001 August (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Princeton Environmental Action, 2001 November (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Principia Public Affairs Conference, 2001 July (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Prorena Smithsonian Tropical Research Institution, 2002 December - 2003 November (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Public Interest in Private Forests, The: Developing Regulations and Incentives, Undated (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Alpha "R" - Dean's Correspondence, 2003 June - 2005 August (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Redefining Progress, 2000 November - 2001 September (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Reforest the Tropics, 2004 September - 2005 May (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Regional Water Authority, 2007 August (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - RenMin University, 2006 July (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - Remote Sensing Workshop, 1999 December - 2000 October (Box 12, Folder 27)
    - Renewable Natural Resources Foundation, 1999-2003 (Box 12, Folder 28)
    - Research Institute for Humanity and Nature (RIHN), 2001 August (Box 12, Folder 29)
    - Resolve, 2003 February (Box 12, Folder 30)
    - Resource Renewal, 2001 October - 2002 December (Box 12, Folder 32)
    - Richard King Mellon Foundation, 2001 February (Box 12, Folder 34)
    - Rivet Entertainment, 38899 (Box 12, Folder 35)
    - Rockefeller Bros. Fund, 2002 February - 2003 June (Box 12, Folder 36)
    - Rockefeller Fund, 1998 May - 2002 June (Box 12, Folder 37)
    - Rockefeller, Wendy Gordon, 37469 (Box 12, Folder 38)
    - Rock Island Company, 37012 (Box 12, Folder 39)
    - Round Table on Sustainable Forests, 37165 (Box 12, Folder 42)
    - Royal Institution World Science Assembly (RiSci), 2003 July - 2003 August (Box 12, Folder 43)
    - Russian Far East, 36800 (Box 12, Folder 46)
    - Alpha "S" - Dean's Correspondence, 2002 November - 2003 June (Box 12, Folder 48)
    - San Francisco Foundation, 37561 (Box 12, Folder 52)
    - Sangha River Network, 36800 (Box 12, Folder 55)
    - Sea Web, 2002 September (Box 12, Folder 63)
    - Search for Common Ground, 2003 March (Box 12, Folder 64)
    - Seattle Conference - University of Washington, 1998 December (Box 12, Folder 65)
    - Sea Web, 2002 September (Box 12, Folder 66)
    - Second Nature, 2000 November (Box 12, Folder 67)
    - Second Nature Workshop - Nov 5-7, 1999, 2000 January-April (Box 12, Folder 68)
    - Second Nature - Education for Sustainability, 1999 September - 2000 July (Box 12, Folder 69)
    - SELS, 2001 December - 2002 January (Box 12, Folder 74)
    - Sierra Club, 2000 January (Box 12, Folder 78)
    - Sierra Pacific Industries, 2001 January (Box 12, Folder 79)
    - Sigmi Xi - The Scientific Research Society, Undated (Box 12, Folder 80)
    - Singapore University, 2001 August (Box 12, Folder 82)
    - Smith Richardson Foundation, 2000 April - 2003 January (Box 12, Folder 87)
    - Smithsonian Tropical Research Institution, 2003 November (Box 12, Folder 88)
    - Society of American Foresters, 2002 July - 2008 June (Box 12, Folder 89)
    - Society of Environmental Journalists, 2000 June - 2004 June (Box 12, Folder 90)
    - Soil and Water Conservation Society, 2000 March (Box 12, Folder 91)
    - Solar Youth, 2003 June (Box 12, Folder 93)
    - South Carolina Coastal Conservation League, 2000 April - 2003 February (Box 12, Folder 95)
    - Sperry Fund Board, 2000 April - 2002 April (Box 12, Folder 97)
    - Spieler Agency, 2002 July (Box 12, Folder 98)
    - Stanford University, 2001 January (Box 12, Folder 99)
    - START, 1999 December (Box 12, Folder 101)
    - State of Connecticut - Department of Higher Education, 2002 January (Box 12, Folder 102)
    - State of World Advisory Commission, 2001 November (Box 12, Folder 103)
    - State of the World Forum, 2001 October (Box 12, Folder 104)
    - Student Conservation Association, 2003 October - 2004 February (Box 12, Folder 114)
    - Student Microfinance Initiative, 2004-2005 (Box 12, Folder 115)
    - Summit Foundation, 2001 July - 2001 August (Box 12, Folder 116)
    - Sustainable Development in a Globalizing World, 2002 January-February (Box 12, Folder 117)
    - Sustainable Forestry Board (SFB), 2002 March-November (Box 12, Folder 118)
    - Switzer Foundation, 37135 (Box 12, Folder 124)
    - Synergos, 2000 March - 2001 April (Box 12, Folder 126)
    - Tata Energy and Resources Institute (TERI), 2002 February - 2004 February (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Tamarack Media, 37926 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Team Lux, 1996 October - 2000 December (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Tellus Institute, 2002 February-October (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - TERI, 2001 November - 2007 December (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Third World Economics, 37226 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Tokyo, 2000 March-April (Box 13, Folder 16)